{
    "subject": "resource/Edward_J._Robeson,_Jr.",
    "predicate": "ontology/almaMater",
    "object": "resource/University_of_Georgia",
    "human_readable": "Edward J. Robeson Jr. attended the University of Georgia.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.988143265247345,
            "question": "Was Edward J. Robeson Jr. a student at the University of Georgia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9686899781227112,
            "question": "Where did Edward J. Robeson Jr. attend university?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9630616903305054,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Edward J. Robeson Jr.'s time at the University of Georgia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9610660076141357,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Edward J. Robeson Jr. and the University of Georgia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9066122174263,
            "question": "What type of institution did Edward J. Robeson Jr. attend?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8774051070213318,
            "question": "What university is associated with Edward J. Robeson Jr.?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8034443259239197,
            "question": "Is there any information about Edward J. Robeson Jr.'s academic background?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7910524606704712,
            "question": "What is known about Edward J. Robeson Jr.'s education?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6918830871582031,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Edward J. Robeson Jr.'s major or field of study?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6894265413284302,
            "question": "Did Edward J. Robeson Jr. pursue higher education?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Edward J. Robeson Jr. attended the University of Georgia.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4942_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information available about Edward J. Robeson Jr.'s major or field of study?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4942_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is known about Edward J. Robeson Jr.'s education?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4942_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information about Edward J. Robeson Jr.'s academic background?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4942_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4942_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4942_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4942_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4942_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4942_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4942_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4942_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4942_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4942_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4942_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation result:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that Edward J. Robeson Jr. attended the University of Georgia. The document from file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4942/re-ranker-msmarco/7.txt states: \"Young Robeson attended the public schools of Quitman, Marietta, and Sparta, Ga., and was graduated from the University of Georgia at Athens in 1910.\""
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe document states, \"Young Robeson attended the public schools of Quitman, Marietta, and Sparta, Ga., and was graduated from the University of Georgia at Athens in 1910,\" which supports the triple that Edward J. Robeson Jr. attended the University of Georgia."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}